[{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664139133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14911,"timeElapsed":79293},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664145745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":6611,"timeElapsed":85906},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664150787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":5039,"timeElapsed":90948},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664162313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":11525,"timeElapsed":102474},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664168676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":6360,"timeElapsed":108837},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664174304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5626,"timeElapsed":114465},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664182123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7817,"timeElapsed":122284},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664189466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7341,"timeElapsed":129627},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664201154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":11686,"timeElapsed":141314},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664208762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5908,"timeElapsed":148922},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664212362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3599,"timeElapsed":152523},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664215316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2952,"timeElapsed":155477},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664223043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7725,"timeElapsed":163204},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664228449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5404,"timeElapsed":168610},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664233034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4582,"timeElapsed":173195},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664237721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4686,"timeElapsed":177882},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664242997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5274,"timeElapsed":183158},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664247581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4582,"timeElapsed":187742},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664255555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5988,"timeElapsed":195716},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664260185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4628,"timeElapsed":200346},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664264550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4362,"timeElapsed":204711},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664269442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4889,"timeElapsed":209603},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664273257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3812,"timeElapsed":213418},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664277456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":4197,"timeElapsed":217616},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664283447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5989,"timeElapsed":223608},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4771,"timeElapsed":228381},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664296716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":8494,"timeElapsed":236877},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664311020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":12732,"timeElapsed":251181},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4036,"timeElapsed":255218},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664318688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3628,"timeElapsed":258849},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664321905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3215,"timeElapsed":262065},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5130,"timeElapsed":267197},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664330817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3778,"timeElapsed":270978},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664337575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6757,"timeElapsed":277736},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4878,"timeElapsed":282616},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664346797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4340,"timeElapsed":286958},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664366079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":17858,"timeElapsed":306240},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664374106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8025,"timeElapsed":314266},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664377373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3265,"timeElapsed":317533},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5052,"timeElapsed":322588},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664386524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4096,"timeElapsed":326685},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3573,"timeElapsed":330259},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664412682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":22582,"timeElapsed":352843},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664416103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3419,"timeElapsed":356264},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664424721,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8616,"timeElapsed":364881},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4945,"timeElapsed":369828},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664435373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4233,"timeElapsed":375534},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664438915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3539,"timeElapsed":379076},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664444665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5748,"timeElapsed":384826},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664449690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5024,"timeElapsed":389851},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664452656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2964,"timeElapsed":392817},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3694,"timeElapsed":396513},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664460318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3964,"timeElapsed":400479},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664464583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4260,"timeElapsed":404744},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664468828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4242,"timeElapsed":408989},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664483648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":13444,"timeElapsed":423809},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664490800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":7151,"timeElapsed":430961},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664496854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6051,"timeElapsed":437015},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664500406,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3551,"timeElapsed":440567},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664507763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7356,"timeElapsed":447924},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664510946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3180,"timeElapsed":451106},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664514328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3382,"timeElapsed":454489},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664518064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3734,"timeElapsed":458225},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664524689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6623,"timeElapsed":464850},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664529005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4312,"timeElapsed":469166},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664540680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":10188,"timeElapsed":480841},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664544275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3593,"timeElapsed":484436},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664547619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3342,"timeElapsed":487780},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664554893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7272,"timeElapsed":495054},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664560107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5212,"timeElapsed":500267},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664563600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3492,"timeElapsed":503761},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664573433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9832,"timeElapsed":513594},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664577455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4020,"timeElapsed":517616},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664583344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5887,"timeElapsed":523505},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664590661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5827,"timeElapsed":530822},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664595401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4738,"timeElapsed":535562},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664599212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3810,"timeElapsed":539373},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664603041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3827,"timeElapsed":543202},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664606532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3489,"timeElapsed":546693},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664610204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3671,"timeElapsed":550365},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664615744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5538,"timeElapsed":555905},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664618925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3179,"timeElapsed":559086},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664622694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3766,"timeElapsed":562855},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664637391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7258,"timeElapsed":577552},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664641160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3767,"timeElapsed":581321},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664644517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3355,"timeElapsed":584678},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664663373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":18855,"timeElapsed":603534},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664668480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5105,"timeElapsed":608641},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664674222,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":5740,"timeElapsed":614383},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664677321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3097,"timeElapsed":617482},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664682358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":5036,"timeElapsed":622519},{"subjectID":"cfg0w0xue7","prolificID":"66baeb26193b68793e6575f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774214d0f0b2ff8e3f0ab08","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664687141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4780,"timeElapsed":627302}]